>> Emily: DEMOCRATIC SOCIALIST
AND FRONT RUNNER IN THE
NEW YORK CITY MAYOR ORAL RACE,
ZOHRAN MAMDANI, SAT DOWN WITH
MARTHA MacCALLUM FOR
RAPID-FIRE INTERVIEW AND AHEAD
OF TONIGHT'S DEBATE.
HE GAVE SEVERAL ELUSIVE ANSWERS
INCLUDING THIS APOLOGY TO THE
MEN AND WOMEN OF NYPD CALLING
THEM AMONG OTHER THINGS RACIST.
WATCH.
DO WE HAVE THAT?
IF NOT, WE WILL GO ON.
MAMDANI SAID TO RELATE TO AWARD
CREDIT FOR CEASEFIRE BETWEEN
ISRAEL AND HAMAS.
WATCH NOW.
WE WILL JUST KEEP --
>> THE POLICE OFFICERS THAT I
SPOKE TO DO NOT WANT BEHIND
CLOSED DOORS APOLOGY BUT BROAD
PUBLIC APOLOGY FOR THE THINGS
YOU SUGGESTED ABOUT THEM.
WILL YOU DO THAT RIGHT NOW?
>> ABSOLUTELY I WILL APOLOGIZE
TO THE POLICE OFFICERS RIGHT
NOW.
THIS IS THE APOLOGY WITH RANK
AND FILE OFFICERS.
I APOLOGIZE THE FACT I LOOKED TO
WORK WITH OFFICERS AND THESE MEN
AND WOMEN WHO SERVE NYPD PUT
THEIR LIVES ON THE LINE EVERY
SINGLE DAY.
>> Emily: WE ALREADY KNEW
THAT.
MAMDANI SAID IT IS TOO EARLY TO
AWARD CREDIT FOR THE CEASEFIRE
BETWEEN ISRAEL AND HAMAS.
WATCH.
>> WHEN IT COMES TO THE
CEASEFIRE, I AM THANKFUL, AND I
HAVE HOPE IT WILL ACTUALLY
ENDURE AND IT WILL BE LASTING.
I CONTINUE TO HAVE CONCERNS
BECAUSE I HAVE SEEN REPORT STILL
IN THE LAST FEW DAYS THAT FIVE
PALESTINIANS KILLED BY ISRAELI
MILITARY PEER THAT GIVES ME
PAUSE ISSUING ANY KIND OF PRAISE
OR CELEBRATION AT A MOMENT WHEN
IT IS STILL SO IN ITS
INFANCY.
>> WOULD YOU GIVE CREDIT TO
PRESIDENT TRUMP OR NOT?
CREDIT OR NOT QUESTION MARKET.
>> IT IS TOO EARLY TO SAY.
IF ENDURING, YOU GIVE CREDIT.
>> Emily: HE ALSO REFUSED TO
ANSWER WHETHER OR NOT HE WOULD
CALL FOR HAMAS TO DISARM.
>> DO YOU BELIEVE HAMAS SHOULD
LAY DOWN THEIR WEAPONS AND LEAVE
THE LEADERSHIP IN GAZA?
I BELIEVE ANY FUTURE IN
NEW YORK CITY IS ONE WE NEED TO
MAKE SURE IS AFFORDABLE FOR ALL
AND PERTAINS TO ISRAEL AND
PALESTINE, PEACE PEER THAT IS
THE FUTURE WE HAVE TO FIGHT FOR
IT.
>> YOU WON'T SAY HAMAS SHOULD
LAY DOWN THEIR ARMS AND GIVE UP
GAZA?
I DON'T HAVE AN OPINION THE
JUSTICE AND SAFETY IN ANYTHING
HAS TO ABIDE BY INTERNATIONAL
LAW AND THAT APPLIES TO HAMAS
AND ISRAELI MILITARY AND ANYONE
YOU WOULD ASK ME ABOUT.
>> Emily: WITH JUST 19 DAYS TO
GO, THE REAL CLEAR POLITICS
AVERAGE SHOWS A LARGE GAP OF
MAMDANI A 717-POINT LEAD OVER
ANDREW CUOMO.
CURTIS SLIWA TRAILS WITH JUST
UNDER 13% SUPPORT.
KELE COME I THINK, FRANKLY, HIS
ANSWERS WERE NOT SURPRISING, BUT
WERE ALARMING FOR MANY REASONS.
HE CONTINUED TO SORT OF HAMMER
THIS INTERNATIONAL COURT THING
AND LAWN AND ORDER BUT I WANT TO
HEAR YOUR TAKEAWAYS HOW YOU
FOUND HIM DURING THIS INTERVIEW
IN HIS ANSWERS?
>> Kayleigh: I FOUND HIM TO BE
DISQUALIFYING AND HERE'S WHY.
YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO LISTEN TO THE
WHOLE INTERVIEW PEER THIS ONE
LINE, MAMDANI SAID I DON'T HAVE
ANY OPINIONS ON THE FUTURE OF
HAMAS AFTER MARTHA PUSHED HIM
TWICE PEER THAT IS A
DISQUALIFYING STATEMENT.
I SAID THIS MANY TIMES ON THE
SHOW AND IT IS DIFFICULT TO HEAR
AND I WILL SAY IT AGAIN
ESPECIALLY CANDIDATE ABOUT TO
TAKE OVER NEW YORK CITY IS ON
THE PRECIPICE OF WARNING MAKES A
STATEMENT LIKE THAT.
BABIES WERE PUT IN EVANS ON
OCTOBER 7TH.
HE DOESN'T KNOW WHETHER HAMAS
SHOULD DISARM? MAYBE I SHOULD
SHARE A FEW DETAILS, BE 23 --
LET'S PULL UP THE PICTURE, HE
WAS PUT IN A CAGE AND RETURNED
HOME 5 FEET HIGH, KEPT IN A CAGE
THE ENTIRE TIME OFTEN TIMES WITH
FIVE HOSTAGES.
IMAGINE TWO YEARS IN A CAGE THIS
MAN WAS HANDCUFFED TO THE CAGE
FOR TWO YEARS AND OFTEN TIMES
WITH FIVE OTHER HOSTAGES.
OKAY, LET'S MEET RON, HIS MOM
SAID HE WAS KEPT BY THE BODIES
OF HOSTAGES IN A ROOM VIOLENTLY
BEATEN, TORTURED, DENIED BASIC
HYGIENE, AND THEN FORCED BACK
FOR LEFT HOME.
WE BROUGHT THE PICTURE SO MANY
TIMES, LITERALLY STRANGLED BY
HAMAS AND KILLED.
AND ZOHRAN MAMDANI CANNOT SAY
WHETHER TERRORIST WHO KILLED
THOSE TWO LITTLE BOYS WERE
DISARMED?
YOU WERE DISQUALIFIED FROM
LEAVING A GROCERY STORE.
YOU SHOULD BE DISQUALIFIED OUT
OF POLITE SOCIETY.
THOSE TWO LITTLE BOYS SHOULD BE
HERE AND NO TERRORISTS SHOULD
HAVE ARMS.
>> Emily: TOM, I WANT TO PLAY
A LITTLE BIT IN KEEPING WITH HIS
ANTI-ZIONISM AND ANTI-ISRAEL,
ANTI-BENJAMIN NETANYAHU AND
ANTI-SEMITISM, HIS RESPONSE
WHETHER HE WOULD TRY TO ARREST
IS RELIEF PRIME MINISTER IF HE
EVER CAME TO NEW YORK CITY.
WATCH.
>> YOU SAID YOU WOULD ARREST
BENJAMIN NETANYAHU IF HE CAME TO
THE UNITED STATES.
>> THIS IS A CITY THAT BELIEVES
IN INTERNATIONAL LAW AND WANTS
TO UPLIFT AND UPHOLD THOSE
BELIEFS.
>> THE UNITED STATES DOESN'T
STAND BY INTERNATIONAL CRIMINAL
COURT APPEARANCE.
>> THE CRIMINAL COURT HAS ISSUED
A WARRANT FOR THE REST OF
BENJAMIN NETANYAHU.
>> THE UNITED STATES --
>> AS IT HAS FOR VLADIMIR PUTIN
MY SAID I BELIEVE WE SHOULD
UPHOLD ARREST WARRANTS BY THE
NATIONAL COURT.
>> Emily: I FIND THAT TELLING,
TOM, HE OBVIOUSLY DOESN'T KNOW
THE LAW OR UNDERSTAND USE TO
SOFTBALL ENVIRONMENTS WHERE HE
CAN PLAY ON TIKTOK, CREATE MEANS
AN IMPRESSIONABLE 20-YEAR-OLDS
TO THE EAST VILLAGE.
HE HAS NO IDEA WHEN PRESSED WITH
THE FACTS, THE LAW OR REALITY IN
ANY WAY WHAT TO DO.
I SAW HIM AS ABSOLUTELY
FLOUNDERING AT BEST.
>> Tom: HE WAS FLOUNDERING BUT
HE SEES THE FINISH LINE.
STAY ON PACE, GET ACROSS THE
FINISH LINE.
TRY NOT TO ANSWER THE QUESTION
SPIRIT THE THING IS, EVERY
ANSWER HE GAVE GAVE SO MUCH AMMN
TO ANDREW CUOMO, BUT I DON'T SE.
IT'S NOT ENTIRELY HIS FAULT.
I KNOW HE'S TALKING BUT I DON'T
SEE HIM.
I HAVE NOT SEEN ANDREW CUOMO
SINCE THE PRIMARIES BECAUSE THIS
GUY SUCKS UP ALL THE AIR.
HE IS SO OUTRAGEOUS, EVERYTHING
HE SAYS IS A NEWS HEADLINE AND
WHAT IS ANDREW CUOMO GOING TO
DO?
>> Harris: WE DON'T SEE
ANDREW CUOMO BECAUSE HE DOESN'T
WANT TO BE A PART OF THE
CAMERAS.
COME ON, GOVERNOR OF THE STATE
AND DONE SO MUCH, WHERE IS HE?
>> Tom: IT'S CRAZY.
>> Harris: SO THAT WAS PART OF
IT.
I APOLOGIZE, AND I AM WILLING TO
WORK WITH POLICE OFFICERS WAS
HIS ANSWER UPON BEING PRESSED
OVER AND OVER BY
MARTHA MacCALLUM ABOUT KEEPING
THE CITY SAFE WITH
LAW ENFORCEMENT.
LOOK, HE'S WILLING TO THWART THE
FEDERAL LAW FOR THE COUNTRY NOT
SIGNING ONTO THE ICC AND DO WHAT
HE WANTS TO DO.
NOW, HE LOVE TO SIDELINE THE
OFFICERS HE IS WILLING TO WORK.
THESE MEN AND WOMEN ALREADY HAVE
JOBS.
HE IS THE ONE WHO WANTS THE JOB
TO BE ABLE TO LEAD THE CITY.
HE IS NOT REALLY INTERESTED IN
ANYBODY EXCEPT FOR WHAT HE'S
GOING TO DO WHEN HE COMES IN.
IT IS NOT GOING TO BE THE BEST
INTEREST OF KEEPING PEOPLE SAFE.
OR HOLDING FEDERAL LAWS AT HAND.
WILL HE PERSONALLY SIGN ONTO THE
INTERNATIONAL COURT?
I MEAN, IS HE GOING TO SIGN ONTO
THE ICC?
>
>> Emily: BE SEATED TO YOUR,
GROUNDSWELL OF SUPPORT AND A LOI
NOTICED THEY ARE POP-UPS AND
A LOT OF DIFFERENT APPS
INCLUDING PERIODICALS IN THE
CITY WHERE THERE IS ADS FOR HIS
COLORING BOOK AND HIS CHILDREN'W
WITH THE THEME ON IT FLOODING
EVERYWHERE.
SO, THERE IS REALLY BLANKETING
OCCURRING FRANKLY, VENOM, UNDER
WHICH AVERAGE NEW YORKERS
COME I DON'T THINK UNDERSTAND
THE DETRIMENT HE WOULD BE TO
EVERYONE'S SAFETY LET ALONE THE
JEWISH PEOPLE HERE IN THIS CITY
AND THE BUSINESSES AND THE LIKE.
IT IS A VERY SHINY VENEER ON A
VERY TERRIFYING MONSTER.
>> Arthel: I MEAN, LISTEN,
SHOULD HAMAS BE DISARMED?
YES.
SHOULD HE HAVE GIVEN
PRESIDENT TRUMP CREDIT FOR HIS
FIRST PHASE OF THE MIDEAST PEACE
DEAL? YES.
SIMPLE ANSWERS.
JUST ANSWER YES OR NO.
VERY SIMPLE.
HERE IS THE THING, HE IS TRYING
TO GET THIS JOB TO RUN THE
WONDERFUL CITY, ANTIMARKET AND
INTERNATIONAL CITY SO PEOPLE
WATCHING MARTHA'S INTERVIEW WANT
TO KNOW WHAT IS GOING TO
HAPPEN IN THE CITY NOT JUST
BECAUSE THOSE WHO LIVE HERE
BUT THOSE WHO COME TO VISIT.
SO HE DID NOT ANSWER WHAT IS HIS
PLAN FOR NEW YORKERS, HOW WILL
HE MAKE THE CITY AFFORDABLE, HOW
DOES HE PLAN TO WORK WITH NYPD
TO MAKE THE CITY SAFER LIKE IT
WAS BEFORE COVID?
I FELT SAFE THEN.
HOW WILL HE TACKLE ALL OF THESE
ISSUES? THESE ARE THINGS WHETHER
YOU LIVE HERE OR VISIT THIS
GREAT CITY, YOU NEED TO KNOW
THOSE ANSWERS.
>> Emily